lt is written
in the Buddhist Canon...
The flag is still.
The wind is calm.
lt is the heart of man
that is in turmoil.
ASHES OF TIME REDUX
lt is the year of a total eclipse.
Drought sweeps the land.
Drought means problems.
Problems mean good business.
l'm from White Camel Mountain.
My name is Ouyang Feng.
l specialize in solving problems.
By the Iooks of you,
I'd say you're about forty.
In those forty years...
there must be peopIe you wish
you had never Iaid eyes on.
Maybe they hurt you.
Maybe you even considered...
kiIIing them.
But you didn't have the nerve...
or couIdn't be bothered.
ActuaIIy kiIIing
is no big deaI.
Now I have a friend
who knows some martiaI arts.
He's a IittIe down on
his Iuck these days.
For a smaII fee, he'II be happy
to rid you of that person.
Think about it.
Actually, killing isn't easy.
But to survive, it's
a risk many are willing to take.
After leaving White Camel Mountain...
l travelled to this desert...
to start a new life.
JINGZHE
SPRING AWAKENS
lt's the 6th day of the 2nd lunar month.
The insects are awakening.
Every year around this time,
a friend comes to visit.
His name is Huang Yaoshi.
He's a strange man.
He always appears from the East.
lt's a routine he's kept up for years.
This time he came to deliver a gift.
Someone I met recentIy...
gave me this bottIe of wine.
She said this wine is magic.
One cup and you'II forget your past.
I thought it was nonsense.
How couId such a wine exist?
She said the root of Man's probIems...
is memory.
Without a past...
every day wouId be a new beginning.
WouIdn't that be great?
The bottIe was meant for you.
But you wouIdn't mind sharing it...
wouId you?
l don't fall
for this kind of nonsense.
So l didn't have a sip.
But it seemed to work.
That night, Huang began
to lose his memory.
Do you remember how we met?
I don't quite recaII.
Then how did you get here?
I don't remember.
Why are you staring at the bird cage?
Because it Iooks famiIiar.
He got very drunk that night.
He rode off at dawn.
l don't know what
was troubling him...
but it probably
had to do with a woman.
A month later, Huang Yaoshi
turned up in the South...
in the hometown
of his best friend.
He visited once before
for his friend's wedding.
He spent time with the couple.
One day, his friend
left town suddenly.
Then Huang left too,
and never returned.
May I offer you a drink?
Just water for me.
We know each other, don't we?
More than that.
You were once my best friend.
But not anymore.
Why are you here?
I met someone recentIy...
who gave me this bottIe of wine.
One cup and you'II
forget your past.
I tried it.
It works.
WouId you Iike a taste?
Do you know the difference
between water and wine?
Wine warms the spirit.
Water onIy brings on a chiII.
WiII I ever see you here again?
No.
l once took an oath.
lf l ever saw this man again,
l'd kill him.
But l didn't follow through.
Because by the time we met again,
l could no longer see.
So what are you, man or woman?
I am the princess...
of the great Murong CIan.
You dare insuIt me thus?
Don't you know I'II kiII you?
You're drunk.
Huang Yaoshi was once wild and free.
People fell for him,
and often got hurt.
That night,
Huang was nearly killed.
Every year there are months when
no one seems to need my services.
Last year, business
was slow when spring came.
For a month,
l had only one customer.
I want you to kiII someone.
His name is Huang Yaoshi.
He's one of
the best swordsmen around.
It won't be an easy job.
Money is no object.
There's onIy one condition.
I decide how he dies.
I want his death
to be as painfuI as possibIe.
What did he do to deserve this?
He Ieft my sister...
for another woman.
He called himself Murong Yang,
the only son of the Murong Clan.
He had met Huang Yaoshi at the Peach
Blossom Grove outside Gusu City.
lt was the 4th day of the 1st lunar
month. The first day of spring.
The almanac read...
''The East wind warms.''
lt's a day for new beginnings.
That night,
Huang played a joke on him.
If you have a sister...
I'II marry her.
Fine.
I'II hoId you to your word.
Yet I warn you,
do not break your word.
For if you do...
I wiII kiII you.
They arranged to meet his sister.
But Huang Yaoshi never showed.
Did my brother come to see you?
Who's your brother?
His name is Murong Yang.
The name rings a beII.
Did he ask you to kiII a man?
I forget.
Mark my words!
I'II kiII you
if you accept his offer.
Your brother is a generous man.
I can't afford to turn him down.
Big spenders Iike him
are scarce these days.
If you reject him...,
I'II pay you doubIe
to cover your Ioss.
But I do have one condition.
You must kiII someone for me...
my brother, Murong Yang!
You two have an odd reIationship.
You sure you hate
your brother that much?
Yes!
He won't Iet me be with Huang Yaoshi.
He thinks I beIong to him.
Therefore he must die.
Has my sister caIIed upon you?
Yes.
If you so much as covet her...
I'II kiII you.
What a caring brother.
She's the onIy famiIy I have.
I must protect her.
-What did she want from you?
-To kiII someone for her.
Someone caIIed Murong Yang.
Huang Yaoshi must be behind this.
With or without him,
she'd do the same.
She wants to be free of you.
I'II never aIIow that,
as Iong as I Iive.
You saw my brother today,
didn't you?
He toId you?
Why didn't you kiII him?
Who wiII pay me if I do?
KiIIing your brother is no sweat,
because he has a weakness.
You know what that is?
It's you.
I toId him you wanted him dead
just to see his reaction.
Ever think he doesn't want you
to be with Huang...
because he wants you for himseIf?
If that's the case,
how strongIy does he want you?
He wants us to be together forever.
Then he must want you very much.
I know.
But I don't want him.
I onIy have feeIings for Huang.
He must be heartbroken.
So what?
My sadness is unbearabIe.
Why shouId I be aIone in my misery?
I want him to know what it's Iike
to be rejected by the one you Iove.
You're a crueI woman.
-And if he kiIIs himseIf?
-That serves him right!
Why are you asking me aII this?
Your brother asked me a question.
It took me a Iong time
to figure out the answer.
The most painfuI way
to kiII a person...
is first to kiII
the person he Ioves most.
But I can't do that.
If I kiII you,
how wouId I get paid?
Right?
Someone's trying to kiII me.
Why?
They say I'm the woman
Huang Yaoshi Ioves most.
Don't Iet them kiII me.
That evening, she refused to leave.
l gave her some wine
to calm her down.
A few drinks later,
she fell asleep.
Where are you hiding my sister?
What makes you think that?
I know you're the Iast person
she saw before she disappeared.
She did show up one night.
She said her Iife was
in danger and needed to hide.
But she Ieft afterwards.
Didn't she go home?
My sister has offended no one.
Why wouId anyone want to kiII her?
She said it's because she's
the woman Huang Yaoshi Ioves most.
Nonsense.
If Huang Ioves her,
why did he Ieave her?
Some peopIe don't reaIize
who they Iove...
untiI they've Ieft
that person behind.
Maybe Huang's Iike that.
He's not.
What makes you so sure?
Because he's in Iove
with another woman.
People always find ways
to mask their pain.
Actually, Murong Yin and Murong Yang
were just two sides of one person.
Hiding behind these two identities
was a wounded soul.
You're drunk, Mr. Murong.
Mister?
You are mistaken.
I'm not Mr. Murong...
but the princess
of the great Murong CIan.
My name is Murong Yin.
And who might you be?
You don't remember me?
You once promised to marry me.
How couId I forget you?
That's so?
That day you passed
through Gusu City.
We drank together
in the Peach BIossom Grove.
You were drunk.
You touched my face.
And you said
if I had a sister...
you'd marry her.
You knew I was a woman in disguise.
Why did you say that?
A drunk man's words
can't be taken seriously.
Those words have kept me waiting
for you aII this time.
I asked you to take me with you,
but you refused.
You said your heart did
not have room for two.
SureIy you Ioved Murong Yin.
How couId you faII in Iove
with another woman?
You know I went Iooking
for that other woman?
When I heard rumor
she was the one you Ioved most...
I went to kiII her.
But I couIdn't go through with it...
because that wouId onIy prove
the rumor correct.
I've asked myseIf so many times...
am I reaIIy
the woman you Iove most?
But I no Ionger want to know.
If I ever ask you this question,
pIease Iie.
No matter how your heart rebeIs...
pIease teII me I'm
the one you Iove the most.
That night passed slowly.
Probably because l seemed to be
talking to 2 people at the same time.
l could no longer distinguish
Murong Yin from Murong Yang.
Murong Yin?
Murong Yang?
TeII me,
who do you Iove the most?
Who eIse but you?
Once, a woman asked me this question.
But l didn't answer.
Speaking as Huang Yaoshi...
l realized it wasn't so hard
to say those words.
As l lay sleeping that night,
l felt someone touch me.
l knew l wasn't the man
she wanted to touch.
But just as she was
imagining l was another man...
l was dreaming of another woman.
Her hands were soft...
like the hands
of my brother's wife.
After that night, no one saw
Murong Yin or Murong Yang again.
A few years later, legend spread
of a strange sword master...
with a mysterious past.
lt's said she practiced her
swordplay on her own reflection...
because she could find
no worthier opponent.
XIAZHI
SUMMER RISES
What do you want?
I want to avenge my IittIe brother.
What happened to him?
A band of swordsmen passed
by a few days ago.
My brother offended one of them.
They kiIIed him.
ShouIdn't this be a matter
for the IocaI magistrate?
They're in the miIitia.
The magistrate wouIdn't
dare do a thing.
How much can you pay?
We're a poor famiIy.
AII I've got are these eggs
and my muIe.
Before she died, my mom gave me
this muIe as my dowry.
To avenge your brother...
you need money.
No one's going to take on
those swordsmen for a muIe.
Vengeance has a price.
If you weren't so pretty...
I wouId've toId you to forget it.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not hinting at anything.
But you shouId know...
that you're worth
much more than a muIe.
You understand?
I'm not that kind of woman.
If money's aII you want...
I'II wait here...
untiI someone eIse comes to heIp.
I'm not sure if she
was just naïve...
or if she really had
nothing better to offer.
From up here...
she looks a lot like
someone l knew.
During the nights that followed,
l had a recurring dream.
l dreamed of the peach blossoms
in my hometown.
l suddenly realized...
l hadn't been back to White
Camel Mountain for many years.
Something wrong with your eyes?
I've had bad eyesight
since I was smaII.
The doctor said
by thirty I'd be bIind.
How oId are you?
AImost thirty.
What brings you here?
The peach bIossoms bIoom beautifuIIy
every spring in my hometown.
I want to see them once more
before I go bIind...
but I'm aImost penniIess now.
They say you soIve
probIems for peopIe.
Can you heIp me?
A friend of mine kiIIed
some bandits a few months back.
Their gang shouId return
to avenge them soon.
My friend's gone.
The viIIagers are starting
a coIIection...
to hire a swordsman for protection.
I've heard of a IocaI swordsman
who's supposed to be fast.
-Is he stiII here?
-Why do you care?
I want to see just how fast he is.
I shouIdn't have come.
It's too Iate now.
Let's Ieave it at an arm.
No.
Let's Ieave it at...
your Iife!
You misunderstood.
I shouIdn't have come because
you're not a worthy opponent.
I said Iet's Ieave it at your arm,
but you offered up your Iife.
Can you heIp me, sir?
Although he was a down-and-out
swordsman...
he lived a very disciplined life.
Everyday he'd come by for
a meal and a drink...
and leave at sunset.
Why do you keep
staring at that girI?
She reminds me of someone.
Your wife?
If you miss her so much,
why Iive Iife on the road?
She's in Iove with my best friend.
When wiII those bandits get here?
ProbabIy within the next few days.
The sooner the better.
I don't want to miss
the peach bIossoms.
Flowers bloom in their season.
But bandits are harder to predict.
He waited outside
the village everyday.
Each day's wait lasted
longer into the night.
Though he lit a lamp after sunset...
l knew
he couldn't see at night.
Don't you Iike me?
You want to go home?
Yes.
-Are you married?
-Why?
I bet you Iove your wife very much.
You couId say that.
Then why did you Ieave her?
WouId you mind treating me
to another drink?
You seem to be in a drinking mood.
I might not be abIe
to drink again tomorrow.
My guess is they'II arrive
before dawn.
I'II get you a Iantern.
Don't bother.
You can't see anymore, can you?
I can, if the sun is bright.
Pray tomorrow's a cIear day.
If I don't return by sunset...
pIease take a message
to someone for me.
His name is Huang Yaoshi.
TeII him a woman's waiting
for him in my hometown.
l don't know why l did that.
l couldn't control myself.
As l walked away...
l felt the girl's tears
slowly drying on my face.
l wondered if my woman
would shed any tears for me.
People say if a sword
strikes fast enough...
the blood spurting from the wound
will sigh like a breeze.
Never had l imagined the first
time l heard that sound...
it would come from
the spurting of my own blood.
BAILU
AUTUMN TURNS
This man is Hong Qi.
He's very quick with his saber,
but he didn't like wearing shoes.
While l knew he could make me
a lot of money...
he always made me uneasy.
A fortune teller once warned me...
''Avoid the number seven
or anyone with the name of Qi.''
When l first met him,
he was fresh from the countryside.
Do you know why
I asked you over to eat?
No.
Because I know you're hungry.
I've had my eye on
you for a whiIe.
You've been sitting by that
waII aII day, too weak to move.
And you don't Iook sick.
I've seen a Iot
of young men Iike you.
You know a few sword moves,
so you think you're invincibIe.
But this is a tough Iine of work.
Being a swordsman keeps
you from doing a normaI job.
Farming's beneath you.
Banditry is not honorabIe.
Street performing is a joke.
So how do you earn a Iiving?
Even the best swordsman has to eat.
I've got the perfect job for you.
The money's good and
it's honorabIe. What do you say?
Yes?
Think about it, but be quick.
As you know, your stomach
wiII be growIing again soon.
Soon after Hong Qi arrived,
the bandits returned.
Before l took him
to see the villagers...
l bought him a pair of shoes...
because there's quite
a difference...
between the price of a swordsman
with shoes and without.
So you think ten taeIs
of siIver is too much?
You can aIways
find someone cheaper.
Look, there's some now.
They're not even wearing shoes.
Pay them a few bucks
and they'II jump on the offer.
But how can you trust a swordsman...
who can't even afford shoes?
What if he takes a beating
and teIIs the bandits you hired him.
Then what?
Now, I'm not saying
my friend is the best.
What I'm saying is this, when the
Iives of your famiIy are at stake...
don't you think, you shouId put
your faith in someone with shoes?
To prepare him for the job...
l brought Hong Qi
to see something.
-Why the corpse?
-Because this corpse can taIk.
Two days ago,
he fought the bandits.
He thought he couId take them aII.
He was wrong.
See this sIash?
It was the fataI bIow.
UnIike the other wounds,
it cut from right to Ieft.
It's unique.
That means the guy
who struck the fataI bIow...
onIy needed to strike once.
When you fight the bandits...
Iook out for one person...
the Ieft-handed swordsman.
If I die, don't put me on dispIay.
I don't want to be a taIking corpse.
The 1 5th day of the 6th lunar month.
lt was sunny and windy.
The almanac says,
''The Star of Judgment descends.''
''Blood will flow.
Do not travel far.''
''Chant scriptures
to prevent catastrophe.''
Those who don't bother
counting their money...
will soon lose it all.
Not Hong Qi.
He counted every cent.
This type of person
won't stay long.
The 10th day of the 7th lunar month.
The first day of autumn. Sunny.
The almanac says, ''The breeze cools.
Auspicious for visiting friends.''
''Do not christen new boats.''
Hong Qi?
He's gone.
I doubt he'II come back.
You shouId Iook eIsewhere.
You hear me?
Fooling a woman is never
as easy as you think.
She might seem simple...
but she understood
her husband well.
Because Hong Qi would never
abandon his camel.
I toId you to wait at home.
Why are you foIIowing me?
Go home!
Go!
No!
Go home! Go!
Go home!
Go!
Get going! Move!
She's been waiting outside
for days now.
She doesn't Iisten.
What can I do?
How can I be a swordsman
with a wife in town?
Who says you can't?
Where there's a wiII,
there's a way.
I was once Iike you.
My head was fiIIed with
thoughts of gIory.
So I Ieft my woman at home.
When I returned, I discovered...
that my woman had married
my brother.
It's pointIess to come
here everyday.
I can't heIp you if
you haven't got any money.
Go home.
I'm begging you.
Begging won't heIp.
I'm just a middIeman.
The onIy person that can heIp
you is yourseIf.
Everyone needs something
to live for.
Others may think it's a waste of
time, but it was important to her.
The 1 5th day of the
7th lunar month. Rain.
According to the almanac,
''The Rain Star brings trouble.''
''The Star of Talent presides.''
''Time to cleanse.
Avoid leaving home.''
''Malignance in the north.''
lf l were those swordsmen
from the militia...
l would have refused to die.
All those lives were lost
merely for an egg.
You gained an egg, but Iost a finger.
Was it worth it?
No.
But I feIt aIive.
I was myseIf again.
This shouId have been no sweat.
But I've Iost my speed.
I was quick because
I never hesitated.
If it feIt right, I'd do it.
I never cared about the money.
I thought I'd aIways be that way.
Then that girI asked me for heIp...
and I knew I was a changed man.
I turned her down...
because I knew you wouId.
I hated myseIf for it.
I confused myseIf with you.
I'd Iost my reaI seIf.
I don't want to be Iike you...
because I know you'd never ever
risk your Iife for an egg.
That's the difference between us.
PIease heIp Hong Qi!
He's hurt bad, isn't he?
-PIease get a doctor.
-A doctor? That costs money.
Damn shame I don't have any eggs.
Otherwise I'd Iend you a few...
since you're so good
at manipuIating peopIe with them.
I won't heIp him
because he didn't Iisten to me.
You're responsibIe for this.
You save him.
You come to me onIy
because you're desperate.
I've been waiting for this moment.
You once toId me you'd
never seII yourseIf.
WeII, Iet's see now
if you can stiII keep your word.
-What's on your mind?
-Nothing.
Don't do anything for my sake.
If I die...
I'II die happy.
I heIped you for an egg.
I've eaten it.
You don't owe me anything.
Remember,
don't do anything stupid.
From that day on,
l never saw that girl again.
I don't think I can
use my saber anymore.
You don't need to use a saber.
Even a Iook can kiII.
Losing a finger
wiII heIp your reputation.
You can raise your fee.
What's the matter?
Homesick?
If you get homesick so easiIy,
why'd you Ieave in the first pIace?
You ever wonder what Iies
beyond this desert?
Another desert.
lt's a question everyone
asks at some point in life.
They see a mountain and want
to know what's behind it.
l wanted to tell him...
the other side may
just be more of the same.
Looking back, home may
not seem so bad after all.
But he'd never listen.
He was the kind of person
who'd have to see for himself.
Where are you going?
PIaces I've never been.
With Iuck, I'II be famous.
If one day you hear
of a nine-fingered hero...
that'II be me.
And her?
I'II take her aIong.
Like you said, where there's
a wiII, there's a way.
Besides, there's no martiaI arts code
against bringing a wife aIong. Right?
Let's go!
l suddenly understood
why they are a couple.
Because they both
are true to their hearts.
As l watched them leave,
l was filled with envy.
l once had this chance.
l don't know why
l let it slip away.
The day they left,
a southerly wind was blowing.
They chose to walk into the wind.
lt was the 1 5th day
of the 8th lunar month.
The almanac had this to say...
''The Chamber Star presides.
Fortune favors the north.''
Hong Qi joined the Gang
of Beggars three years later.
He became their leader and was
known as the Beggar of the North.
ln his later years, he dueled with
Ouyang Feng on Snow Mountain...
where they took each other's life.
After Hong Qi left,
the rain poured nonstop.
Every time it rains,
l think of her.
She once loved me.
Maybe it was just coincidence...
but every time l left
on a journey, it would rain.
She said it was because she was sad.
Later, she married my brother.
The day of their wedding,
l left White Camel Mountain.
You can ask me today,
tomorrow, whenever.
My answer will be the same.
l won't go with you.
l ask for the last time.
Will you come with me?
l'm staying. Remember, from
now on l belong to your brother.
There's only one man who
can touch me, and that's him.
No other man has that right.
LICHUN
WINTER FADES
Why are you staring
at my scarf?
It beIongs to my husband.
Why do you have it?
Is he dead?
l hadn't seen peach blossoms
in years.
So the following spring, l visited
the blind swordsman's hometown.
To my surprise,
l didn't find any peach blossoms.
There's no point for me
to keep it anymore.
Only when l left did l understand...
this place never had
any peach blossoms.
''Peach Blossom'' was merely
the name of a woman.
As that woman wept...
l suddenly realized why Huang Yaoshi
came to see me every year.
He's an odd child, isn't he?
He keeps to himself.
l'm not sure
if he's arrogant or shy.
He never asks for what he wants.
He expects to be pIeased.
You have to offer it to him.
At first, I induIged him.
GraduaIIy, I Iost my patience.
Though l've always loved her,
l've kept it a secret.
Because l know untasted fruit
is the sweetest.
Every time she gazed fondly
at her son...
l knew she was thinking
of someone else.
l envy Ouyang Feng.
l long to be loved...
yet only manage to hurt others.
I aIways thought you two
wouId stay together.
Why didn't you marry him?
He never toId me how much
he wanted me.
Some things don't need to be said.
But it's what I needed to hear.
He was too proud to say it.
He took it for granted
that I wouId marry him.
He never imagined
I'd marry his brother.
On my wedding night,
he asked me to Ieave with him.
But I refused.
Why did he want me onIy
when he couIdn't have me?
If that's the way
he was going to be...
I decided I wouId never
Iet him have me.
lf love is a contest,
l'm not sure she's the winner.
But l know for certain...
l've been a loser from the start.
This woman made me
love peach blossoms.
l'd see her each year when
the peach blossoms bloomed.
l visited Ouyang Feng...
because she wanted to know
how he was doing.
Thanks to Ouyang Feng...
l had an excuse
to see her every year.
Do you know what's the most
important thing in my Iife now?
Your son, no doubt.
I once thought so.
But as I watch him grow day by day...
I know someday he'II Ieave me.
Nothing reaIIy matters anymore.
I used to think some words
were so important.
Once spoken they'd Iast a Iifetime.
But Iooking back, I reaIized
it makes no difference.
Everything changes.
I aIways thought I was the winner...
untiI one day I Iooked
in the mirror...
and saw the face of a Ioser.
During the best years of my Iife...
the person I Iove was not by my side.
WouIdn't it be wonderfuI
if we couId go back to the past?
You're his good friend.
Why haven't you toId him I was here?
I made you a promise.
So I kept siIent.
You're too honest.
Not long after, she fell ill
and passed away.
Before she died, she gave me
a bottle of wine to take to him.
She hoped Ouyang Feng
would forget her.
lt's said memory is
the root of Man's troubles.
That year,
l started to lose my memory.
Now, l only recall a vague
fondness for peach blossoms.
Six years later, Huang Yaoshi
retired to Peach Blossom lsland...
and lived as a hermit.
He called himself the Master
of Peach Blossom lsland.
Others knew him
as the Lord of the East.
JINGZHE
SPRING RETURNS
Spring begins.
The insects will soon awaken.
Every year around this time,
a friend comes to visit.
But this year he didn't show.
Shortly afterwards, l received
a letter from White Camel Mountain.
lt said my brother's wife
had died two winters ago.
l knew Huang Yaoshi
wouldn't come again.
Yet still l waited.
For two days and two nights,
l sat at my door.
Watching the shifting clouds,
l realized...
though l lived here a long time...
l'd never really looked
at the desert.
Before, when l saw a mountain
l wanted to know what lay behind.
But not anymore.
Fate made me an orphan.
My parents died young.
My brother raised me.
Being an orphan,
l always had to fend for myself.
l learned the best way
to avoid rejection...
is to reject others first.
This is why
l've never returned home.
lt wasn't bad there.
But what have l to go back for?
l was born under the influence
of a total eclipse.
Love was destined to be out of reach.
That night,
l suddenly needed a drink.
l finished the bottle of magic wine.
l carried on with business as usual.
By the Iooks of you,
I'd say you're about forty.
In those forty years...
there must be peopIe you wish
you had never Iaid eyes on.
Maybe they hurt you.
Maybe you even considered
kiIIing them.
But you didn't have the nerve.
ActuaIIy kiIIing is no big deaI.
No sweat at aII.
Now I have a friend
who knows some martiaI arts.
He's a IittIe down
on his Iuck these days.
For a smaII fee, he'II be happy
to rid you of that person.
Think about it.
But be quick.
If you wait...
When work was not busy, l'd look in
the direction of White Camel Mountain.
l remembered a woman
was waiting for me there.
That magic wine was just
a joke she played on me.
The more you try to forget,
the better you'll remember.
People say...
when you can't have what you want,
the best you can do...
is not to forget.
l don't know why l have
these recurring dreams.
l left the desert
soon afterwards.
The day l left, the almanac
had this to say...
''The Travel Star advances; Fire
Conquers Gold. Fortune lies West.''
Ouyang Feng returned to White
Camel Mountain the following year.
He became known
as the Lord of the West.